
<root>

	<PeopleTalkFirst>
		<Hero name = "Chris">Hey, have you ever heard of the déjà vu effect? Have you ever felt this way?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Security">No, this is the first time I hear about it. What's this?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Chris">In short, this is when a person feels that he has already been in a similar situation or in a similar place, said such things.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Security">Wow, I wonder... never experienced.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Security">...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Security">No, never.</Hero>
	</PeopleTalkFirst>

	<EdWalkUpPeople>
		<Hero name = "">Oh huh, are they going to pity me?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">Let's go.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">Now for half an hour listening to "I'm sorry", "I sympathize" and "how is it, man, it's not fair" and the like.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Hey, hello!</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Ed, where's your smile?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">Okay, coming soon. We have good news for you.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">I won't need to help anyone? Otherwise, I’ll probably refuse right away, I’ve already had enough, to be honest...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">No, don't worry. We are just about this situation.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">In short, it's good that you slept a little, otherwise it happened in the morning...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">At first, when Bob and I entered the office, security and boss were discussing something, but I'm curious enough, and decided to overhear.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">In general, we know that you hacked the locked door.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Yes, Mark came up and said that you didn't just break open the door, but also stole something.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">We obviously did not believe it, because it seemed to us as strange as possible.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">In short, to tell you the essence, listen.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">We convinced the boss that Mark set you up.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">It seems that this trap was not his goal, but the point is that you were in the "right place at the right time".</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Well, your skills also played a role.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">You won't get fired, Ed, you can relax.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Yes, that jerk Mark is fired. Hell, I never liked him.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Even his appearance is so... specific.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">This is how villains usually look.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Yes, that's what I wanted to say.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">So guys, wait a minute.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">So, you mean, boss understood everything and just forgave me?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Yes, he got it. You didn't even know what was behind this door, and you yourself did not even open it.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">I find it hard to believe so far...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">Why? It's really not your fault, so relax.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">And I'm also wondering why you decided to take care of this and help me?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">What a stupid question, Ed?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">Don't make us laugh, dude.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">The answer is pretty simple. You helped us, and we helped you.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Besides, it literally cost us nothing, but you were so worn out helping us.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Not really, of course.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">I find it hard to believe, too.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">Dude, keep it simple, as if you never had friends and you can't believe this.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Well, strictly speaking, I really had not.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Now you have, Ed.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Yes, it's kind of strange, ahah.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Thank you guys.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Seriously, even if it didn't cost you anything. Thank you.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">I wouldn't be here anymore if not for your help.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Really, never mind.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "David">Dude, don't forget you still have a day plan. You're not fired, so get to work, ahaha.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Yeah, right... I totally forgot about that.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Bob">Well... Get to work!</Hero>
	</EdWalkUpPeople>

	<ClickOnWorkspace>
		<Hero name = "">Unexpected, of course.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">This is all so strange.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">Really, as if I'm in a dream.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">Okay, I'll have time to think about it before bed. I have to work, since fate gives me such a chance.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">Maybe I jumped to conclusions about Ari's words last night. All the same, these guys really pulled me out of this situation.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "">This is what it feels like...</Hero>
	</ClickOnWorkspace>

	<SolveDreamPuzzle>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Hey Ed, wake up.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">What?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">I say wake up, sleepyhead.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Am I dreaming? Where am I?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Aahha, you fell asleep at work, right on the table.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">What? Seriously? What day is it?</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Same as before you fell asleep.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Remember, no? You were almost fired today, but nothing happened.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">God, I thought I was dreaming about that...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Damn, I'm already lost in dreams and reality.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">By the way, yesterday I wanted to talk to you about this...</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">What about? About realities and dreams? You are so cute.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Yes, it's just a mismatch in my head.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Okay, let's talk now. Let's go, maybe, towards the house. The working day has already ended.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Already? So fast? I thought I only slept a few minutes.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">I think it is. I was looking at you, you fell asleep very recently, so I think that's okay.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ari">Let's go. Get some fresh air, it's very beautiful there now.</Hero>
		<Hero name = "Ed">Fresh air would be good for me. Need to wake up.</Hero>
	</SolveDreamPuzzle>
	

</root>